Guide to the Time Inc. Reference Files 1907-2015 (bulk 1933-2003) MS 3009-RG 3
New-York Historical Society
- International: Statistics (Offsite-box 514, Folder 16)
- IPC Media: Magazines (Offsite-box 514, Folder 17)
- IPC Media: Misc. (Offsite-box 514, Folder 18)
- Keywords: AOL Time Warner Employee Newsletter: June 2002-Dec. 2002 (Offsite-box 514, Folder 23)
- Keywords: AOL Time Warner Employee Newsletter: Jan. 2003-Dec. 2003 (Offsite-box 514, Folder 19)
- Keywords: AOL Time Warner Employee Newsletter: Jan. 2004-Dec. 2004 (Offsite-box 514, Folder 24)
- Keywords: AOL Time Warner Employee Newsletter: 2006 (Offsite-box 514, Folder 20)
- Keywords: AOL Time Warner Employee Newsletter: 2007 (Offsite-box 514, Folder 21)
- Keywords: AOL Time Warner Employee Newsletter: 2008 (Offsite-box 514, Folder 22)
- Legal: Summaries, mostly year-end (Offsite-box 515)
- Legal: Summaries, mostly year-end [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R6)
- Legal: Misc. (Offsite-box 515, Folder 2)
- Leisure: Misc. (Offsite-box 515, Folder 3)
- Library (Offsite-box 509, Folder 15)
- Life: ABC reports: 1936-1944 (Offsite-box 515, Folder 4)
- Life: ABC reports: 1945-1953 (Offsite-box 515, Folder 5)
- Life: ABC reports: 1954-1964 (Offsite-box 515, Folder 6)
- Life: ABC reports: 1965-1972 (Offsite-box 515, Folder 7-8)
- Life: ABC reports: 1960-1972 (Offsite-box 515, Folder 9-10)
- Life: ABC reports: 1978- (Offsite-box 515, Folder 11-12)
- Life: Advertising: History (Offsite-box 515, Folder 13-14)
- Life: Advertising Rate Cards: 1936-1963 (Offsite-box 515, Folder 15)
- Life: Advertising Rate Cards: 1964-1972 (Offsite-box 515-516)
- Life: Advertising Rate Cards: 1978 and later (Offsite-box 516, Folder 2-4)
- Life: List of Advertisers: 1970-1972, 1979 (Offsite-box 516, Folder 5-6)
- Life: List of Advertisers: 1980-1988 (Offsite-box 516, Folder 7-8)
- Life: Art (Offsite-box 516, Folder 9)
- Life: Articles Reports: 1956-1957 (Offsite-box 516, Folder 10)
- Life: Bookazines, books, other specials: 2001- (Offsite-box 516, Folder 11)
- Life: Brand Marketing: 2003- (Offsite-box 516, Folder 12)
- Life: Business Development: 2003- (Offsite-box 516, Folder 13)
- Life: Circulation: Newsstand Prices (Offsite-box 516, Folder 14)
- Life: Circulation: Newsstand Sales (Offsite-box 516, Folder 15)
- Life: Circulation: Misc. (Offsite-box 516-517)
- Life: Edit: Briefings: Office Newsletter: 1940 (Offsite-box 517, Folder 2)
- Life: Edit: Briefings: Story Behind the Story Index: 1950-1959 (Offsite-box 517, Folder 3)
- Life: Story Behind the Story in Life: 1950 (Offsite-box 517, Folder 4)
- Life: Story Behind the Story in Life: 1951 (Offsite-box 517, Folder 5)
- Life: Story Behind the Story in Life: 1952 (Offsite-box 517, Folder 6)
- Life: Story Behind the Story in Life: 1953 (Offsite-box 517, Folder 7)
- Life: Story Behind the Story in Life: 1954 (Offsite-box 517, Folder 8)
- Life: Story Behind the Story in Life: 1955 (Offsite-box 517, Folder 9)
- Life: Story Behind the Story in Life: 1956 (Offsite-box 517, Folder 10)
- Life: Story Behind the Story in Life: 1957 (Offsite-box 517, Folder 11)
- Life: Story Behind the Story in Life: 1958 (Offsite-box 517, Folder 12)
- Life: Story Behind the Story in Life: 1959 (Offsite-box 517, Folder 13)
- Life: Edit: Briefings: Editorial News: 1942-1949 (Offsite-box 517, Folder 14)
- Life: Edit: Briefings: Edit Side and Deadline: 1959-1960 (Offsite-box 517, Folder 15)
- Life: Edit: Briefings: Edit Side and Deadline:: 1961-1965 (Offsite-box 517, Folder 16)
- Life: Edit: Briefings: Selling With This Week's Life: 1962 (Offsite-box 518, Folder 1)
- Life: Edit: Briefings: Selling With This Week's Life: 1963 (Offsite-box 518, Folder 2)
- Life: Edit: Briefings: Selling With This Week's Life: 1964 (Offsite-box 518, Folder 3)
- Life: Edit: Briefings: Selling With This Week's Life: 1965 (Offsite-box 519, Folder 2)
- Life: Edit: Briefings: About The Current Issue of Life and On The Edit Side: 1966-1968 (Offsite-box 518, Folder 4)
- Life: Edit: Issue Analysis: 10/78-5/81 (Offsite-box 518, Folder 5-6)
- Life: Edit: Houses and Housing: Dream House concept (Offsite-box 518, Folder 7)
- Life: Edit: Houses, Housing, Buildings: Lists of articles compiled by the Time Inc. Index Department (Offsite-box 518, Folder 8)
- Life: Edit: Letters Reports (Offsite-box 518, Folder 9)
- Life: Edit: Life as a Weekly: Gaines memo 1990 (Offsite-box 518, Folder 10)
- Life: Edit: Misc. (Offsite-box 518)
- Life: Edit: Misc. [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R6)
- Life: Edit: Reporters' Manual: 1965 (Offsite-box 518, Folder 14)
- Life: Top Stories (Offsite-box 518, Folder 15)
- Life: Edit: Text Department: Indexes (Offsite-box 518, Folder 16)
- Life: Edit: Text Department: Bylines, Staff and Non-Staff: 1957-1962 (Offsite-box 518-519)
- Life: Editor's Note: Index (Starting 11/30/1962) (Offsite-box 519, Folder 3)
- Life: Educational Reprints (Offsite-box 519, Folder 4)
- Life: History (I) (Offsite-box 519, Folder 5-7)
- Life: History (II) (Offsite-box 519, Folder 8-9)
- Life: History: Closing: May 2000 (Offsite-box 519, Folder 10)
- Life: History: Rebirth of Life: 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 519, Folder 11)
- Life Magazine: Test issue as weekly: April 1, 1991 (Offsite-box 519, Folder 12)
- Life: Logo as of July 1973 (Offsite-box 519, Folder 13)
- Life: Misc. (Offsite-box 519, Folder 14-15)
- Life: Mock-Ups (Offsite-box 519, Folder 16)
- Life: Newspaper supplement introduced 2004 (Offsite-box 519, Folder 17)
- Life: Old Life: Weekly humor magazine (Offsite-box 519)
- Life: Old Life: Weekly humor magazine [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R6)
- Life: Picture Collection (Offsite-box 519, Folder 19)
- Life: Photographers (Offsite-box 519-520)
- Life: Production (Offsite-box 520, Folder 2)
- Life: Promotion (Offsite-box 520, Folder 3)
- Life: Prospectus Copies (Offsite-box 520, Folder 4)
- Life: Stamp: 1998 (Offsite-box 520, Folder 5)
- Life: Statistical Studies: Historical Data Book (Offsite-box 520, Folder 6-7)
- Life: Statistical Studies:Misc. (Offsite-box 520, Folder 8-10)
- Life: Sunday Supplement: 2003- (Offsite-box 520, Folder 11)
- Life: War Art: 1941-1945 (Offsite-box 520, Folder 12)
- Life: International: ABC Reports (Offsite-box 520, Folder 13-14)
- Life: International: Advertising Rates: 1946-1958 (Offsite-box 520, Folder 15)
- Life: International: Advertising Rates: 1959-1962 (Offsite-box 520, Folder 16)
- Life: International: Advertising Rates: 1963-1965 (Offsite-box 520, Folder 17)
- Life: International: Edit Summaries (Offsite-box 521, Folder 4)
- Life: International: Misc. (Offsite-box 521, Folder 5-6)
- Life: Picture Sales (Offsite-box 521, Folder 7)
- Life: Spanish (Offsite-box 521, Folder 8-9)
- Line Magazine (Offsite-box 521, Folder 10)
- Listen 2 This (Offsite-box 521, Folder 11)
- Little Brown (Offsite-box 521, Folder 12)
- Logos (Offsite-box 521, Folder 13)
- Look Magazine (Offsite-box 521, Folder 14)
- Luce (Henry R.) Stamp (Offsite-box 521, Folder 15)
- Magazine Administrative Services: 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 521-522)
- Magazine Administrative Services: Facilities Design and Management: FACS Facts (Newsletter) (Offsite-box 522, Folder 2)
- Magazine Group (Offsite-box 522, Folder 3-4)
- Magazine: Manufacturing and Distribution (Offsite-box 522, Folder 5)
- Magazine: Development (Offsite-box 522, Folder 6)
- Magazine and the Press: Civil Liberties Study: 1948 (Offsite-box 522, Folder 7)
- Magazine and the Press: Financial Study of 11 Major Publications: 1950 (Offsite-box 522, Folder 8)
- Magazine and the Press: History (Offsite-box 522, Folder 9)
- Magazine and the Press: MAB Study: The National Magazine and American Life: 1947 (Offsite-box 522, Folder 10)
- Magazines and the Press: Schools of Journalism (Offsite-box 522, Folder 11)
- Magazines and the Press: Statistics (Offsite-box 522, Folder 12)
- Magazine and the Press: World War II (Offsite-box 522, Folder 13)
- Magazine and the Press: Time Inc.'s Influence: 1940 (Offsite-box 522, Folder 14)
- Magazine and the Press: Misc. (Offsite-box 522, Folder 15-16)
- Makeover: Magazine Development: Single Issue only: Summer 1994 (Offsite-box 522, Folder 17)
- Management Executive Committee: 1942-1944 (Offsite-box 522, Folder 18)
- Management Executive Committee: 1945-1947 (Offsite-box 522, Folder 19)
- Management Executive Committee: 1948-1950 (Offsite-box 522, Folder 20-21)
- Management Executive Committee: 1951-1952 (Offsite-box 522, Folder 22)
- Management Executive Committee: 1953 and Later (Offsite-box 522, Folder 23)
- Maps (Offsite-box 522, Folder 24)
- Manhattan Cable T.V.: Misc. (Offsite-box 523, Folder 1)
- Manhattan Cable T.V.: Press Releases (Offsite-box 523, Folder 2)
- Manhattan Cable T.V.: Program Guides (Offsite-box 523, Folder 3)
- March of Time: Film: Index with Synopses (Offsite-box 523, Folder 4)
- March of Time: Movie: Film Library Index (Offsite-box 523, Folder 5)
- March of Time: Movie: History Film: Produced by Lothar Wolff: 1975 (Offsite-box 523, Folder 6)
- March of Time: Movie: Foreign Versions (Offsite-box 523, Folder 7)
- March of Time: Movie: Film Storage: Morrie Roizman's Inventory (Offsite-box 523, Folder 8)
- March of Time: Movie: Commercial Version: Transfer of Rights to SFM: 1981- (Offsite-box 523, Folder 9)
- March of Time: Movie: Index Supplement (Offsite-box 523, Folder 10)
  Complete contents listed from the commercially marketed sets.
- March of Time: Movie: Awards (Offsite-box 523, Folder 11)
- March of Time: Movie: Fielding, Raymond (Offsite-box 523, Folder 12-13)
- March of Time: Movie: Indexes (Offsite-box 523, Folder 14-15)
- March of Time: Movie: Copyrights (Offsite-box 523, Folder 16)
- March of Time: Movie: Misc.: 1950- (Offsite-box 523, Folder 17-8)
- March of Time: Misc.: 1934-1949 (Offsite-box 523, Folder 19)
- March of Time: Movie: Music (Offsite-box 523, Folder 20)
- March of Time: Movie: "Photo Reporter" and "Scholastic News" (Offsite-box 523, Folder 21)
- March of Time: Personnel Lists: 1944-1948 (Offsite-box 523, Folder 22)
- March of Time: Movie: Statistics (Offsite-box 523, Folder 23)
- March of Time: Radio: History: March 6, 1931-1945 (Offsite-box 524, Folder 1)
- March of Time: Radio: Index: March 1931-March 1933 (Offsite-box 524, Folder 2)
- March of Time: Radio: Index: Oct. 1933-April 1934 (Offsite-box 524, Folder 3)
- March of Time: Index: Oct. 1934-April 1935 (Offsite-box 524, Folder 4)
- March of Time: Radio: Index: Aug. 1935-March 1936 (Offsite-box 524, Folder 5)
- March of Time: Radio: Index: April 1936-Sept. 1936 (Offsite-box 524, Folder 6)
- March of Time: Index: Oct. 1936-April 1939 (Offsite-box 524, Folder 7)
- March of Time: Radio: Index: July 1942-July 1945 (Missing: 10/39-6/42) (Offsite-box 524, Folder 8)
- March of Time: Radio: Misc. (Offsite-box 524, Folder 9)
- March of Time: Television (Offsite-box 524, Folder 10)
- March of Time: Radio: Theses (Offsite-box 524, Folder 11)
- March of Time: Revisited: 1970-1974 (Offsite-box 524, Folder 12)
- Martha Stewart Living Enterprises (Offsite-box 524, Folder 13)
- Memos to Staff: AOL Time Warner: 2001 (Offsite-box 524, Folder 14)
- Memos to Staff: AOL Time Warner: 2002 (Offsite-box 524, Folder 15)
- Memos to Staff: AOL Time Warner: 2003 (Offsite-box 524, Folder 16)
- Memos to Staff: Time Warner: 2004 (Offsite-box 524, Folder 17)
- Memos: Staff: 1940-1949 (Offsite-box 524, Folder 18)
- Memos: Staff: 1950-1959 (Offsite-box 524, Folder 19)
- Memos: Staff: 1960-1969 (Offsite-box 524, Folder 20)
- Memos: Staff: 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 524, Folder 21)
- Memos: Staff: 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 524, Folder 22)
- Memos: Staff: 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 524, Folder 23)
- Memos: Staff: 1977 (Offsite-box 524, Folder 24)
- Memos: Staff: 1978 (Offsite-box 525, Folder 1-2)
- Memos: Staff: 1979 (Offsite-box 525, Folder 3)
- Memos: Staff: 1980 (Offsite-box 525, Folder 4)
- Memos: Staff: 1981 (Offsite-box 525, Folder 5)
- Memos: Staff: 1982 (Offsite-box 525, Folder 6)
- Memos: Staff: 1983 (Offsite-box 525, Folder 7)
- Memos: Staff: 1984 (Offsite-box 525, Folder 8)
- Memos: Staff: 1985 (Offsite-box 525, Folder 9)
- Memos: Staff: 1986 (Offsite-box 525, Folder 10)
- Memos: Staff: 1987 (Offsite-box 525, Folder 11)
- Memos: Staff: 1988 (Offsite-box 525, Folder 12)
- Memos: Staff: 1989 (Offsite-box 525, Folder 13)
- Memos: Staff: 1990 (Offsite-box 525, Folder 14)
- Memos: Staff: 1991 (Offsite-box 525, Folder 15)
- Memos: Staff: 1992 (Offsite-box 525, Folder 16)
- Memos: Staff: 1993 (Offsite-box 525, Folder 17)
- Memos: Staff: Time Inc: 1994 (Offsite-box 525, Folder 18)
- Memos: Staff: Time Inc: 1995-1996 (Offsite-box 525, Folder 19)
- Memos: Staff: Time Inc: 1997-1998 (Offsite-box 525, Folder 20)
- Memos: Staff: Time Inc: 1999-2000 (Offsite-box 525, Folder 21)
- Memos: Staff: Time Inc: 2001 (Offsite-box 525, Folder 22)
- Memos: Staff: Time Inc: 2002 (Offsite-box 525, Folder 23)
- Memos: Staff: Time Inc: 2003 (Offsite-box 543, Folder 1)
- Memos: Staff: Time Inc: 2004 (Offsite-box 543, Folder 2-3)
- Memorandum to Staff: Time Warner: 1989-1991 (Offsite-box 543, Folder 4)
- Memorandum to Staff: Time Warner: 1992 (Offsite-box 543, Folder 5)
- Memorandum to Staff: Time Warner: 1993 (Offsite-box 543, Folder 6)
- Memorandum to Staff: Time Warner: 1996 (Offsite-box 543, Folder 7)
- Memorandum to Staff: Time Warner: 1994-1995 (Offsite-box 543, Folder 8)
- Memorandum to Staff: Time Warner: 1997 (Offsite-box 543, Folder 9)
- Memorandum to Staff: Time Warner: 1998 (Offsite-box 543, Folder 10)
- Memorandum to Staff: Time Warner: 1999 (Offsite-box 543, Folder 11)
- Memorandum to Staff: Time Warner: 2000 (Offsite-box 543, Folder 12)
- Mine: My Magazine, My Way: Time Inc. Content Solutions/Toyota Customized Content Magazine: 2009 (Offsite-box 543, Folder 13)
- Money: Advertising Promotion: Memo to Advertisers: 1994- (Offsite-box 543, Folder 14)
- Money: Adv. Rate Cards (Offsite-box 543, Folder 15)
- Money: Prospectus Copies (Offsite-box 543, Folder 16)
- Money: A.B.C. Reports: 1995-2004 (Offsite-box 543, Folder 17-18)
- Money: A.B.C. Reports: 2005-Present (Offsite-box 543, Folder 19)
- Money: Edit: Graphics (Offsite-box 543, Folder 20)
- Money: Index: July 1973-July 1975 (Offsite-box 543, Folder 21)
- Money: Misc. (Offsite-box 543, Folder 22-23)
- Money for Kids: Premiere Issue: Spring 1993 (Offsite-box 543, Folder 24)
- Money: extraMoney (Distributed to high schools) (Offsite-box 543, Folder 25)
- Money: for Women: Misc.: First issue May-June 2000 (Offsite-box 543, Folder 26)
- Mouth 2 Mouth: First Issue: Spring 1994 (Offsite-box 543, Folder 27)
- Mutual Funds: Misc.: 1998-2002 (Offsite-box 543, Folder 28)
  Last issue: November 2002
- National Portrait Gallery: Time Inc. Cover Art Collection (Offsite-box 543, Folder 29)
- Netscape (Offsite-box 543, Folder 30)
- New Line Cinema (Offsite-box 543, Folder 31)
- Nuts (Offsite-box 543, Folder 32)
- Offices: N.Y.: Time and Life Building: Second Floor Conference Center Exhibit Cases: Records of Archives material on loan (Offsite-box 543, Folder 33)
- Office Buildings: Records: 1950-1972 (Offsite-box 543, Folder 34)
- Office Buildings: United States: State: New York (City): Time and Life Building: 1956-1960 (Offsite-box 544, Folder 1)
- Office Buildings: United States: State: New York (City): Time and Life Building: 1961-1967 (Offsite-box 544, Folder 2)
- Office Buildings: United States: State: New York (City): Time and Life Building: 1968-1973 (Offsite-box 544, Folder 3)
- Office Buildings: United States: State: New York (City): Time and Life Building: 1974-1984 (Offsite-box 544, Folder 4)
- Office Buildings: United States: State: New York (City): Time and Life Building: 1985 (Offsite-box 544, Folder 5)
- Offices: N.Y.: Time and Life Bldg: 1271 Ave of the Americas: Mad Men Television Series (Offsite-box 544, Folder 6-7)
- Offices: Boston (Offsite-box 544, Folder 8)
- Offices: Chicago (Offsite-box 544, Folder 9-10)
  1 audiotape reel: analog, 5 in., 1/4 in. tape. Case labeled: "Cornerstone Ceremony - Chicago Time and Life Bldg - May 13, 1968"
  Unreformatted audiovisual material in the collection is not accessible.
- Offices: N.Y.: Time and Life Bldg: 9 Rock. Plaza (Offsite-box 544, Folder 11)
- Offices: New York City: TandL Bldg: Lobby: Restaurants: La Fonda Del Sol (Offsite-box 544, Folder 12)
- Offices: N.Y.: Time and Life Bldg: 1271 Ave of the Americas: 1956-1979 (Offsite-box 544, Folder 13-14)
- Offices: N.Y.: Time and Life Bldg: 1271 Ave of the Americas: 1980- (Offsite-box 544, Folder 15-16)
- Offices: N.Y.: Time and Life Bldg: 1271 Ave of the Americas: Cafeteria: 1972- (Offsite-box 544, Folder 17)
- Offices: N.Y.: Time and Life Bldg: 1271 Ave of the Americas: Landmark Designation: 2002 (Offsite-box 544, Folder 18)
- Offices: N.Y.: Time and Life Bldg: 1271 Ave of the Americas: Pre-Move (Offsite-box 544, Folder 19)
- Offices: N.Y.: 75 Rockefeller Plaza (Offsite-box 544, Folder 20)
- Office: New York: Time Warner Center: 10 Columbus Circle: 2002- (Offsite-box 544, Folder 21-22)
- Offices: N.Y.: Misc (Offsite-box 545, Folder 1)
- Offices: Misc. (Offsite-box 545, Folder 2)
- Offices: International (Offsite-box 545, Folder 3)
- On (Time Digital) (Offsite-box 545, Folder 4)
- Open House Research Center: 6/25/1996 (Offsite-box 509, Folder 14)
- Outdoor Life: 2000- (Offsite-box 545, Folder 5)
- Panorama (Italian) (Offsite-box 545, Folder 6)
- Parenting Group: Misc. (Offsite-box 545, Folder 7)
- People: A.B.C. reports (Offsite-box 545, Folder 8)
- People: Adv.: Promo: In People Newsletter: 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 545, Folder 9)
- People: Adv.: Rate Cards (Offsite-box 545, Folder 10)
- People: Advertising Promotion: In People Newsletter: 1992- (Offsite-box 545, Folder 11)
- People: Covers: Misc. (Offsite-box 545, Folder 12-13)
- People: Letters: Reports (Offsite-box 545, Folder 14)
- People: Misc.: 1989- (Offsite-box 545, Folder 15-18)
- People: Misc.: 1973-1988 (Offsite-box 545, Folder 17-18)
- People en Espanol (Offsite-box 545, Folder 19)
- People en Espanol: Covers: Misc. (Offsite-box 545, Folder 20)
- People International: People en Espanol, People in Chinese (Offsite-box 545, Folder 21)
- People International: Who Weekly (Offsite-box 545, Folder 22)
- People: Prospectus Copies (Offsite-box 545, Folder 23)
- People: People to People: Staff Newsletters: 1975-1980 (Offsite-box 545, Folder 24-25)
- People: People to People: Staff Newsletters: 1981-1988 (Offsite-box 546, Folder 1-2)
- Personnel and Organization: Benefits: Annual Report of Profit-Sharing Savings Plan: Report by the Adminsitrative Committee (Offsite-box 546, Folder 3)
- Personnel and Organization: Benefits: Time Employees' Profit-Sharing Savings Plan: Annual Report of the Administrative Committee: 1965-1980 (Offsite-box 546, Folder 4-5)
- Personnel and Organization: Benefits: Time Employees' Profit-Sharing Savings Plan: Annual Report of the Administrative Committee: 1952-1964 (Offsite-box 546, Folder 6-7)
- Personnel and Organization: Benefits: Misc.: 1920s-1970s (Offsite-box 546, Folder 8-9)
- Personnel and Organization: Benefits: 1984-1989 (Offsite-box 546, Folder 10-11)
- Personnel and Organization: Benefits: 1990-1999 (Offsite-box 546, Folder 12-13)
- Personnel and Organization: Benefits: 2000- (Offsite-box 546, Folder 14-15)
- Personnel and Organization: Benefits: AOL-TW Founders Grant: Stock Options (Offsite-box 546, Folder 16)
- Personnel and Organization: Department Head Lists: 1940s-1950s (Offsite-box 546, Folder 17)
  Existence and Location of Copies
  Digital copies are available in the N-YHS Digital Collections: Time, Inc. department head lists, 1949-1987.
- Personnel and Organization: Department Head Lists: 1960s (Offsite-box 546, Folder 18-19)
- Personnel and Organization: Department Head Lists: 1970, 1972, 1974 (Offsite-box 546, Folder 20)
- Personnel and Organization: Department Head Lists: 1978 (Offsite-box 547, Folder 1)
- Personnel and Organization: Department Head Lists: 1979 (Offsite-box 547, Folder 2)
- Personnel and Organization: Department Head Lists: 1980 (Offsite-box 547, Folder 3)
- Personnel and Organization: Department Head Lists: 1981 (Offsite-box 547, Folder 4)
- Personnel and Organization: Department Head Lists: 1982 (Offsite-box 547, Folder 5)
- Personnel and Organization: Department Head Lists: 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 547, Folder 6)
- Personnel and Organization: Department Head Lists: 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 547, Folder 7)
- Personnel and Organization: EAP Matters (Offsite-box 547, Folder 8)
- Personnel and Organization: Equaltime (Newsletter) (Offsite-box 547, Folder 9)
- Personnel and Organization: Health Promotion Program (Offsite-box 547, Folder 10)
- Personnel and Organization: Lists: Misc. (Offsite-box 547, Folder 11)
- Personnel and Organization: Managing Your Future (401k Newsletter): 1994- (Offsite-box 547, Folder 12)
- Personnel and Organization: Minorities (Offsite-box 547, Folder 13-14)
- Personnel and Organization: Minorities: A3 (Asian American Association of Time Inc.) (Offsite-box 547, Folder 15)
- Personnel and Organization: Minorities: BE@T (Black Employees at Time) (Offsite-box 547, Folder 16-22)
- Personnel and Organization: Minorities: Coming Out- Gay Issues in America (Offsite-box 547, Folder 23)
- Personnel and Organization: Minorities: Diversity Report (Offsite-box 547, Folder 24)
- Personnel and Organization: Minorities: Hola (Offsite-box 547, Folder 25)
- Personnel and Organization: Minorities: Lesbians and Gay Men (Offsite-box 547, Folder 26-27)
- Personnel and Organization: Minorities: Lesbians and Gay Men [RESTRICTED until 2065] (Offsite-box R6)
- Personnel and Organization: Minorities: OUT @ Time Inc. (Offsite-box 548, Folder 1)
- Personnel and Organization: Memoranda: 1992- (Offsite-box 548, Folder 2)
- Personnel and Organization: Miscellaneous: 1936-1986 (Offsite-box 560, Folder 7-9)
- Personnel and Organization: Miscellaneous: 1985- (Offsite-box 548, Folder 3-5)
- Personnel and Organization: Newspaper Guild Contracts (Offsite-box 548, Folder 6-10)
- Personnel and Organization: Newspaper Guild: Job Classification (Offsite-box 548, Folder 11)
- Personnel and Organization: Newspaper Guild: On Time (Offsite-box 548, Folder 12-14)
- Personnel and Organization: Newspaper Guild of New York: Local 3 Bulletin (Offsite-box 548, Folder 15-18)
- Personnel and Organization: Newspaper Guild: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 548, Folder 19)
- Personnel and Organization: Policy Handbooks (Offsite-box 548, 560)
- Personnel and Organization: Policy Manual: 1976 (Offsite-box 560, Folder 3)
- Personnel and Organization: Policy Manual: 1974 (Offsite-box 560, Folder 4)
- Personnel and Organization: Policy Manual: 1969 (Offsite-box 560, Folder 5)
- Personnel and Organization: Policy Manual: Corporate Group: 1985 (Offsite-box 560, Folder 6)
- Personnel and Organization: Recreational Activites (Offsite-box 560, Folder 10)
- Personnel and Organization: Time Inc. Compliance Office: Standards of Business Conduct: 2002 (Offsite-box 560, Folder 11)
- Personnel and Organization: Wartime: 1941-1945 (Offsite-box 560, Folder 12)
- Personnel and Organization: Women (Offsite-box 560, Folder 13)
- Personnel and Organization: Work-Life Initiatives (Offsite-box 560, Folder 14-15)
- Personal Finance Management Group: Misc. (Offsite-box 560, Folder 16)
- Photographers, Photography (Offsite-box 560, Folder 17-18)
- Photographers Represented by Time Pix (Offsite-box 560, Folder 19)
- Picture Week: Covers (Offsite-box 560, Folder 20)
- Picture Week: Significant Issues (Offsite-box 560, Folder 21)
- Picture Week: Misc. and Test Issue: 9/30/1985 (Offsite-box 560, Folder 22)
- Pictures, Inc. (Offsite-box 561, Folder 1)
- Pioneer Press (Offsite-box 561, Folder 2)
- Popular Science: 2000- (Offsite-box 561, Folder 3)
- President: ABC (Offsite-box 561, Folder 4)
- President: Misc. (Offsite-box 561, Folder 5)
- President's Committee (Offsite-box 561, Folder 6)
- Printing Developments Inc. (PDI) (Offsite-box 561, Folder 7-8)
- Production: 1992- (Offsite-box 561, Folder 9)
- Prospectus Copies: Time Inc. Titles: Fortune-Life-Money-People-SI-Time (Offsite-box 561, Folder 10)